(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
「Fuwawaだよー！」
I'm Fuwawa!
「Mococoだよー！」
I'm Mococo!
「FUWAMOCO Abyssgard!」
FUWAMOCO Abyssgard!
「ばうばう！」
Bau bau!
「Mococo ready!」
Mococo ready!
「Fuwawa ready!」
Fuwawa ready!
「I'm ready!」
I'm ready!
「いくよー！」
Here we go!
「Happy birthday, FUWAMOCO!」
Happy birthday, FUWAMOCO!
「フワモコ、お誕生日おめでとうー！」
FUWAMOCO, happy birthday!
「フワモコ、お誕生日おめでとう！」
「お誕生日おめでとう！」
Happy birthday!
「フワモコちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう、ばうばう！」
FUWAMOCO-chan, happy birthday, bau bau!
「お誕生日おめでとうございます！」
Happy birthday!
「FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival 2026!」
FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival 2026!
「ラフィアンズー！」
Ruffians!
「It's showtime!」
It's showtime!
「一緒にいたいよ」
I want to be with you
「Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau bau」
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau bau
「Yeah, future is bright (Yeah, just us two) Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters」
Yeah, future is bright (Yeah, just us two) Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters
「FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!」
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
「ばうばうばうばうばうばうばうばう！」
Bau bau bau bau bau bau bau bau!
「My heart 'n soul 'n tail are FUWAWA (yay)」
My heart 'n soul 'n tail are FUWAWA (yay)
「I'm so fluffy that even I could float away」
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
「Just call for me, we're only a bark away」
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
「Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe」
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
「FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!」
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
「I love being tricky, doggie kisses are for me」
I love being tricky, doggie kisses are for me
「I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me」
I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me
「Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere」
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
「FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you」
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
「Barking, oh, so merrily」
Barking, oh, so merrily
「It's showtime!」
It's showtime!
「一緒にいたいよ」
I want to be with you
「Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau bau」
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau bau
「一生涯, sing with you」
For a lifetime, sing with you
「Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow」
Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow
「It's showtime!」
It's showtime!
「一緒にいたいよ」
I want to be with you
「Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau bau」
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau bau
「Yeah, future is bright」
Yeah, future is bright
「Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters」
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters
「Woooo...」
Woooo...
「ばう！」
Bau!
「Woooo...」
Woooo...
「ばう！」
Bau!
「Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell」
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
「Holding back, doggy dog hope kept sealed away (Bau!)」
Holding back, doggy dog hope kept sealed away (Bau!)
「Bouta burst, fluff & fuss, we're meant to be free」
Bouta burst, fluff & fuss, we're meant to be free
Make a break for it, it's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement, dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin', but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why, いつだって, it's that day! (Today!)
And that's why, it's that day! (Today!)
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! Bau bau!
一生涯、walk with you!
For a lifetime, walk with you!
Good times and bad times, it doesn't matter!
いつだって, it's that day!
It's that day!
Lifetime, showtime, everyday! Bau bau!
Yeah, 二人は
Yeah, just us two,
Happy lucky puppy sisters!
Fuwamoco, bau bau!
Everybody, bau bau!
Hallo hallo, bau bau!
ダメダメノンノン, don't touch the ears!
Don't touch the ears!
もふもふノンノン, don't touch the tail!
Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ Fuwawaだよ, Bau!
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! Bau!
フワワじゃないよ Mococoだよ, Bau!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo! Bau!
魔界の番犬シスターズ, Yeah! Bau!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! Bau!
And together, we're... Fuwamoco!
Gather up our dreams,
and suddenly you'll come to realize
there's as many as there are stars
illuminating the night sky.
Never-ending dreams,
we don't know if they all can be achieved,
but we'll keep on going furr-ever,
together here with you!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたい
It's showtime! I want to be with you!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
Fuwa fuwa! Moco moco! Hand in hand with you,
bring your smile, rain or shine,
we'll protect it, won't forget our pledge to you!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたい
It's showtime! I want to be with you!
Lifetime, showtime, any time, bau-bau!
一生涯、sing with you
For a lifetime, sing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow.
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you!
Lifetime, showtime, any time, bau-bau!
And together, we're...
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters!
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
Fuwamoco! (Bau bau!)
ラフィアンズ！オラフィアンズ！
Ruffians! Orufians!
ようこそ！FUWAMOCO Wacha★Wacha Birthday Festivalへ！
Welcome to our FUWAMOCO Wacha★Wacha Birthday Festival!
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate our birthday with us, Ruffians!
始まりました！
It's started!
今日は私たちの3Dライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to our 3D live concert today!
Well, to continue off from yesterday's Friday show, tonight again, today we have a big concert!
Can you believe it? It's already been three years!
Right! Our third birthday in hololive English!
But, Mococo-chan, we can't forget the really important things, right?
Huh? Introductions! Oh, yeah! Okay!
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
We are hololive English Advent's twin demon guard dog sisters! Together we're... FUWAMOCO! Bau bau!
And we have an amazing birthday festival stage today!
An amazing stage!
With such a big concert, too!
Mococo is also... Fuwawa! Mococo-chan! Okay, here we go! Three, two, one...
Bau bau!
It's so big and wide! Yeah!
Thank you all for this big stage today!
But singing and dancing today is not just going to be us, right?
No! We're also here with some very special guests too!
そう、今日はとっても素敵なゲストさんも来てるから、ぜひ楽しみにしてくださいね！
Yes, we have some very wonderful guests with us today, so please look forward to it!
そして、もう一人、謎のゲストさんも！誰かな？
And another one, a mysterious guest! Who could it be?
ラフィアンズ！オラフィアンズ！
Ruffians! Orufians!
But a birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right?
Right! Something very important!
Ah, I think you know what... but...
ハッシュタグ！
Hashtags!
Right up here, you can see our birthday hashtag: #FWMCbday26 !
That it is! Please, please post your thoughts!
And take lots of photos! Screenshots are great too!
そう！ハッシュタグで感想を呟いてください！
Yes! Please tweet your thoughts with the hashtag!
写真もね！後でポチしに行くからね！
And photos too! We'll go check them out later!
Bau bau! We will check all your thoughts after the show!
Oh, also...
We're going to be having a special membership-only concert right after this!
So don't miss it, okay? Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
最後にはメンバー限定のアンコールライブもありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
And finally, there will be a member-exclusive encore live, so please come watch!
Ruffians! Woah!
You know, it is a concert after all, right?
So we get singing a little more, yeah?
Yeah, yeah!
Woah!
Oh, for this next song...
I think we need a special guest, right?
Yeah! Okay, let's call her on together!
Okay! Ready...
Calli-senpai!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Bow wow!
みなさん！
Everyone!
Bow wow!
Today only, I am also a dog.
Bow wow wow wow!
死神ドッグ！
Reaper dog!
Yeah!
Thank you for the invite, happy birthday!
Thank you for inviting me, I'm happy to be here!
What's up, Ruffians!
But I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, huh?
I do!
Wow, look at this logo. What does it say? Check it out!
With respect!
With respect, respect, respect, respect!
You know, it would be pretty cute if we matched, right?
Right!
But, maybe...
We just go run and get changed real quick!
Oh, okay. Entertain her for a second.
You entertain them!
Okay.
You can do it! They won't bite, they won't bite.
Okay, okay! Bow wow!
Ruffians! Welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
I can't... I'm sorry, I can't do it!
I did my best!
We're matching, matching!
Matching, matching!
Cute!
Yeah!
We matched!
Tripling?
Tripling!
Tripling? Oh, that has a nice ring to it.
Yeah, yeah!
This next song...
is one that Fuwamoco...
we wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
Yes! Yes!
Something nostalgic, and I think you'll be able to see why. There's some rap in it as well!
But it's also very cute, right?
次歌う曲は、カリ先輩と一緒にずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です！
The next song we'll sing is a favorite song that we've always wanted to sing with Calli-senpai!
Yeah, yeah!
It's both cute...
and cool!
But I think, you know, it shares...
an important part that...
you know, you should be proud of what you like, right?
The important meaning of being proud, being strong about what you like, yeah!
Yeah, your likes!
You know, whether it be games...
anime...
idols...
figures...
or maybe even...
VTubers!
Nice, nice!
After all, life is more fun when you're just true to yourself, right?
Definitely, I agree.
So we're going to sing this song for you, okay?
Okay! Let's do the title call together, okay?
聞いてください！
Please listen!
Like! Like! Like!
Comic, I like it!
Music, I like it!
Game, I like it!
Animation, I like it!
Figure, I like it!
Movie, I like it!
Wonder, I like it!
Hobby, I like it!
Go go go go go go go go
Do you like it? I like it!
人生楽しんだもん勝ちの裏技をさあ
Come on, let's look at the secret trick of winning by enjoying life
好きなもの好きって言えたらそれスーパーノヴァ
If you can say you like what you like, that's a supernova
解像度上昇させてもっともっと上をさあ
Increase the resolution and aim higher and higher
まだできたて書きかけの螺旋みたいな歌を歌うんだ
Sing a song like a spiral that's still fresh and half-written
123！毎度毎度気付けばもう時間が一瞬でしょ？
123! Every single time, you realize time passes in a flash, right?
脳に刺激溜め込むそう今すぐさあミックスさせちゃう！
Storing up stimulation in the brain, yes, let's mix it up right now!
君が部屋にいたってメン限すればコンサート
Even if you're in your room, if it's member-only, it's a concert
いつだってonly only only onlyな脳内へエスケープ
Escaping to inside the brain that is always only only only only
I like it! I like it! 好きになれば
I like it! I like it! If you fall in love with it
きっと全てがカラフルで
Surely everything will be colorful
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even the stardust
光る宝物さ
is a shining treasure
I like it! I like it! 君に会えた
I like it! I like it! I got to meet you
やっと今日からロジックね
Finally starting from today, it's logic, isn't it?
ほらキラキラ夢みたい
Look, sparkling, it feels like a dream
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hold you soon
あれもこれも欲しくて
Wanting this and that
神様に祈ってる
I'm praying to God
ねぇ 好きでしょうがない
Yeah, I can't help but love it
次は何にしようかな
What should I do next?
ある日変わる毎日 留まる愛を 飛ばす愛言葉 Like! Like! Like! Get!
One day, daily life changed. Sending love to that stagnant love with the password 'Like! Like! Like!' Get!
360度パノラマ全方向大好きの陣
360-degree panorama, in all directions, the formation of love!
何か一つでもいいから のめり込める自分のアイテム Like a superstar, fire man!
Even just one thing is fine, my own item that I can lose myself in, like a superstar, fire man!
無敵キャンディ 誇り抱いて大体制
Invincible candy, hold your pride in a grand system!
望んでる過程もきっと 現在が愛おしくなるはずなのさ
Even the journey you wished for will surely make the present feel endearing.
なろうとしてなるもんじゃない 人生楽しんで歩こうじゃない
It's not about trying to become something, shouldn't we just walk and enjoy life?
Oh! 自分に素直であれ
Oh! Be true to yourself.
スポットライト 僕らを照らせ
Spotlight, shine on us!
今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ Get down!
Today, I'll just keep shouting my love! Get down!
Singing a song for you
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out your hand...
きっと 全てがミラクルで
...surely everything will be a miracle!
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life is a dream-like story!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I got to meet you!
ずっと 離さないでいてね
Never let me go, okay?
ほら キラキラ虹みたい 世界は回りだす
Look, sparkling like a rainbow, the world starts to spin!
いくよー！
Here we go!
冷たーい！
It's cold!
水鉄砲パワー！
Water gun power!
そーれ！
Take that!
いやいやいや！
No, no, no!
好き 好き 好き 勝負大歓迎 手に入れたいこの感情
Like, like, like, battles are welcome! I want to grasp this feeling!
歯止めとっさに真剣勝負
Instantly braking for a dead-earnest showdown!
ためらわないのがいいんでしょ？
It's best not to hesitate, right?
そう 恋ももっと実験
Yeah, love is also more of an experiment!
でもそれがボクらの等身大！
But that's our true-to-life size!
Get this, Bust this 世界を確認
Get this, Bust this, confirming the world!
いわゆるひとつの萌え要素！
So to speak, a single moe element!
素直になれたなら Happy Days
If we could be honest, those would be Happy Days!
I Like It! I Like It! 好きになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If you fall in love...
きっと 全てがカラフルで
...surely everything will be colorful!
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ 光る宝物さ
Lucky! Lucky! Even stardust becomes a shining treasure!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I got to meet you!
やっと「今日からよろしくね」
Finally, 'let's get along from today on!'
ほら キラキラ夢みたい 早く抱きしめたい
Look, sparkling like a dream, I want to hold you close soon!
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out your hand...
きっと 全てがミラクルで
...surely everything will be a miracle!
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life is a dream-like story!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I got to meet you!
ずっと 離さないでいてね
Never let me go, okay?
ほら キラキラ虹みたい 世界は回りだす
Look, sparkling like a rainbow, the world starts to spin!
How was it, Ruffians?!
Yeah! Woohoo! Oh my god!
I like Fuwamoco! / Thank you Calli-senpai!
Bye-bye Calli, bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Thank you!
Please listen to our next song, Je t'aime Je t'aime!
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime / Lyrics: Tommy february6 / Music: MALIBU CONVERTIBLE
[Song: Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime / Lyrics: Tommy february6 / Music: MALIBU CONVERTIBLE]
街角に並ぶ
Lined up on the street corner...
映画のポスター
...are movie posters.
もうこの街にも
To this town as well...
秋が来る
...autumn is coming.
ドアの向こうに
Beyond the door...
ため息を返す
...I sigh in return.
キャンセルしないで
Please don't cancel.
mon amour, pour toi
ハートのミニポケットに
In the mini pocket of my heart...
隠した写真 誰も知らない
...is a hidden photo that no one knows about.
本気の恋
A genuine love.
神様は気づいている
God has already noticed it.
Je t'aime, Je t'aime
叶わない夢なんて
A dream that won't come true...
見たくないわ
...is something I don't want to see.
でも ロマンス 目覚めてゆく
But my romance is starting to awaken.
“愛してるわ”
“I love you”
クレープに描く
Drawn on a crepe...
愛の傘の下で
...under an umbrella of love.
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of the endless rain...
Je t'aime, Je t'aime
空っぽな夜に
On an empty night...
したくはないから
...I don't want it to be like this,
ほんの5分でも
Even if it's only for five minutes,
会いたい
I want to see you.
キャンディショップも
The candy shop,
レコードショップも
and the record store too...
あなたがいないと
...are so boring...
つまらない！
...without you around!
ジャケットのポケットに
In my jacket pocket,
入れたままのコインに
with the coin left inside,
賭けるわ 恋の行方
I'll wager the path of our love.
神様が知っている
God already knows.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
退屈な恋なんて
A boring love is something...
したくはないわ
...I don't want to experience.
あっという間に溺れてく
Before I know it, I'm drowning in it.
「今がすべて」
"This moment is everything."
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before my café au lait...
しまうその前に
...gets completely cold,
もう一度KISSして
kiss me one more time.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
物語に
On our story,
鍵をかけて
lock it up.
de jour en jour…
あなたのことばかりを夢見ている
I dream only of you.
mon amour…
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
叶わない夢なんて
Dreams that won't come true...
見たくはないわ
...are something I don't want to see.
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is awakening.
「愛してるわ」
"I love you."
クレープに描く愛の傘の下で
Underneath the umbrella of love I draw on a crêpe,
止まぬ雨の音
hear the sound of the endless rain.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
mon amour pour toi
退屈な恋なんて
A boring love is something...
したくはないわ
...I don't want to experience.
あっという間に溺れてく
Before I know it, I'm drowning in it.
「今がすべて」
"This moment is everything."
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before my café au lait...
しまうその前に
...gets completely cold,
もう一度聴かせて
let me hear it once more.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
La la la...
ばうばう！
Bau bau!
Look at the sunset!
Oh, it's setting already, huh?
Perfect timing!
Well, that last song was "je t'aime ★ je t'aime"!
What did you think, huh?
What did you think, Ruffians?
It's a little bit more nostalgic,
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic of a song.
You know, with some city pop vibes too!
Yeah, the choreography is cute too, right?
Well, we hope it made you feel nice...
アキロゼ先輩とAZKi先輩は、とっても魅力的なお姉さんたちなので...
Since Akirose-senpai and AZKi-senpai are such very charming older sisters...
あら、そうですか？
Oh, is that so?
ちょっとこの曲で行こうかなと思いました。
I thought we should go with this song.
あらあら。
Oh my.
ちょっとね、日も暮れてますし、ちょっとロマンチックになりましたね。
Well, the sun has set, so it's gotten a bit romantic.
そう、ちょっぴりセクシーかも！
Yes, maybe a little sexy!
セクシーかも？セクシーな曲？
Maybe sexy? A sexy song?
そういうことある？ / おねがいしたいことがありまして...
Is that possible? / There's something we'd like to ask of you...
アキロゼ先輩、この曲を歌う前に、少し、あの、セクシーなウォームアップを...
Akirose-senpai, before we sing this song, could you do a little... um, sexy warm-up...
お！セクシーウォームアップ！
Oh! A sexy warm-up!
いいですか？ / セクシーウォームアップ！オッケー！
Is that okay? / Sexy warm-up! Okay!
じゃあまずセクシーな体を作るために...
Well, first, to build a sexy body...
自分のボディを撫でて...
stroke your own body...
撫でて... 頭撫で撫で、足から...
Stroke... Stroke your head, from your legs...
足から！
From the legs!
撫でる！
Stroke!
撫でてみて！やってみて！
Try stroking! Give it a try!
はずかしい！
How embarrassing!
アキロゼ先輩みたいに...
Just like Akirose-senpai...
あ、モコちょっとできてる？
Ah, is Moco doing it a bit?
いいよ！オッケー、いいよ！
Great! Okay, that's good!
撫でるのがセクシー...
Stroking is so sexy...
下から、お尻をこう、セクシーに...
From below, sexy hips like this...
もう一回、もう一回！
One more time, one more time!
フワー！ / ちょっと違うかな？
Fuwah! / Maybe a bit different?
そう。
Yes.
AZKiちゃんもなんかセクシーだけど可愛い。
AZKi-chan is also somehow sexy yet cute.
やっぱこうやって、お尻とか...
After all, like this, the hips...
お尻、お尻！ / あ、尻尾！
Hips, hips! / Ah, the tail!
尻尾ふりふり！
Wagging our tails!
尻尾ふりふりウォームアップ！
Tail-wagging warm-up!
ウォームアップ、ウォームアップ！ / ふりふり、ふりふり...
Warm-up, warm-up! / Wiggle, wiggle...
いいよいいよ、いい感じ！
It's good, it's good, looking great!
できてきた！
I'm getting it!
いい感じになりましたね！
We've got a good vibe going!
はい、次の曲行きましょうか！
Yes, let's move on to the next song!
それでは、聴いてください。 DISCOTHEQUE!
Now then, please listen to: DISCOTHEQUE!
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
(DISCO LADY DISCO LADY)
(DEEP EMOTION DEEP EMOTION)
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN', let's dance
弾ける BEAUTY LADY
Bursting BEAUTY LADY
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn in a sweet dream
そっと彩りたいの
I want to gently color it
グラマラスなくちびる
Glamorous lips
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
Pink, glossy nails
ガラスの向こう側に映る素顔
The true self reflected on the other side of the glass
シュールなDays キミだけにSO 見せていたい
Surreal Days, I want to show it only to you
心の中
In my heart
瞳の奥
In the depths of my eyes
AH 傍にいて欲しいよ
AH, I want you to be by my side
月のMIRROR BALL 照らされて
Illuminated by the moon's MIRROR BALL,
MY DARLIN'
ねぇ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょ
Hey, let's have a vivid love
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Bursting SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn in a sweet dream
そっと彩る MY LOVE
Gently coloring MY LOVE
ほら 世界は変わる
Look, the world is changing
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
(SEXY FEELING)
(CHU CHU...CHU CHU...)
ドラマティックな情熱
Dramatic passion
褪せない デジャヴ 見続けたくて
An unfading déjà vu, I want to keep seeing it
カラフルなSWEETY STORY
A colorful SWEETY STORY
心深く 刻み込む
Deep in my heart, I carve it in
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if a little darkness visits
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant the love spell
そう、きっと
Yes, surely
果てない空 星屑のSHOWERが
In the endless sky, a SHOWER of stardust
降り注ぐ
Pours down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
So, let's aim for the HAPPY STATION
50/50あわせて
50/50, put it together
100%以上の愛
Love that is over 100%
揺るぎなくここにあると
I believe that it is surely here, unwavering
私思ってる
I believe
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
マイルール・フレッシュ・シルブプレ
My rule, fresh, s'il vous plaît
ワン・ステップ・トゥー・ブラン・ニュー・ワールド
One step to a brand new world
君にありのままで 好きでいてほしいと
I want you to love me just as I am
願いは...
My wish is...
素敵なら...
If it's wonderful...
Just trust me, Just love me...
My darling もっと一緒に踊りましょう
My darling, let's dance together more
Secret night 素敵な
On this wonderful, secret night
波打つ胸 デコレーション
My racing heart is decorated
ふたりのハートで合図
Signaling with our two hearts
重なり合わせて
Let's overlap them
My darling ねえ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
My darling, let's have a vivid love
はじける Sexy Beauty
A bursting sexy beauty
生まれ変わっても甘い夢
A sweet dream even if we are reborn
そっと彩る My love ほら
Softly coloring my love, look
世界は変わる
The world changes
チュル チュル チュル パヤパ
Chu-lu chu-lu chu-lu pa-ya-pa
燃え尽きるわ
I will probably burn out...
この恋たぶん
...in this love
どんな終幕が来ようと 覚悟してる
Whatever ending comes, I am prepared
余裕なんて ほとんどない
I have almost no leeway
必死でしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately clinging on
貴方の目
Your eyes,
優しく抱きよせる腕
the arms that gently hold me close
すべてがすべてが 初めてのFall in loveだったわ
Everything, everything, it was my first time falling in love
Kiss me 離さないで
Kiss me, don't let go of me
Kiss me 自然なままで
Kiss me, naturally as I am
この不安を拭いとって
Wipe away this anxiety
ねぇ ねぇ
Hey, hey...
Touch me その指先
Touch me, with those fingertips
Touch me その眼差しで
Touch me, with those eyes
この私を包み込んで
Wrap me up entirely
Please... Please...
愛してる
I love you
よみがえるわ
It all comes back to me...
昨日のこと
...everything that happened yesterday
あんなに心が揺れたの 初めてだもん
It's the first time my heart has shaken like thatSafe
寂しすぎて 時に怖い
It's too lonely, sometimes I'm scared
二人で居れないこの時が
This time when we can't be together
雨の朝
A rainy morning,
暖かな部屋でコーヒー
having coffee in a warm room
大人のフリから 本当の大人になれそう
From acting like an adult, I might become a real adult
Kiss me 危険な程
Kiss me, to a dangerous degree
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me, with a sweet kiss
この願いを全部叶えて
Make all these wishes of mine come true
ねぇ ねぇ
Hey, hey...Confused
Knock me その魂で
Knock me, with that soul of yours
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the windowSafe
この私を安心させて
Put my mind at ease
Please... Please...
愛してる
I love you
Kiss me いけないほど
Kiss me, to a dangerous degree...
Kiss me 甘いくちづけ
Kiss me with a sweet kiss...
こんな願いごと全部叶えてね
Please grant all of these wishes of mine, okay?
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Knock me その魂で
Knock me with that soul of yours...
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on my window...
今度私を安心させて
This time, put my mind at ease...
Please
Please... Please...
愛してる
I love you!
ワン、ツー！アイマリー！レッツゴー！
One, two! I'm ready! Let's go!
Please join! Triangle Dreamer!
日毎に日毎に募る乙女心
Day by day, a maiden's feelings grow...
同じクラスの斜め前の新しい人
The new person sitting diagonally in front of me in class...
格好良くはない だけど優しい
He's not good-looking, but he's kind...
いつも頼れる彼
...A reliable boy I can always count on.
放課後 アイスソーダの帰り道
On the way home after school with an ice soda...
何でも話せる親友の女の子
...With my best girl friend whom I can tell anything to.
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて
She's great at sports, smart too...
女子力マックスです
...And her femininity is at its absolute maximum!
どこにでもある よくあること
It's a very common story that you can find anywhere.
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she says...
「あのね、実は私、好きな人がいるの」って
"You know, actually, there's someone I like..."
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, are you serious!?
三角関係 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is so capricious!
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses in an instant.
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
A cliché flag just like in a manga...
まさかね自分が立てちゃうなんて残念すぎます
I can't believe I raised it myself, it's so unfortunate!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is so unstable!
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
Just kidding... No, "just kidding" won't save us from this!
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship swaying back and forth...
なんか青春しちゃいます
It feels like we're really living our youth.
わたし困っちゃいます
I'm totally in a bind!
乾杯です お似合いすぎるお似合いコンビ
Cheers! They look so incredibly perfect together...
哀しいけど どこかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's sad, but deep down, that's not what I really feel...
って言うか既に応援モード
Or rather, I'm already in support mode...
むしろ清々しい
...In fact, it feels quite refreshing!
だけど彼女は不思議な顔
But she has a puzzled look on her face...
真剣な目で「そうじゃなくて、私、あなたが好き。ごめん」って
With serious eyes, she says, "No, not him... I like you. Sorry."
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, are you serious!?
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is so capricious!
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses in an instant.
わたし あなた 彼女とわたし
Me, you, her and me...
超絶複雑百合展開は想定外です
This incredibly complex yuri development is totally unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is so unstable!
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
Just kidding... No, "just kidding" won't save us from this!
解けないパズル 与えたもうた
Who gave us this unsolvable puzzle?
神よ 恨んじゃいます
Oh God, I'm going to resent you!
わたし 悩んじゃいます
I'm so conflicted!
あわわ すごいやばい
Awawa, this is so bad!
好きだよ 好きだけど
I like you, I like you, but...
ってそういう意味じゃなくて！
That's not what I meant!
だって女の子同士だし！
I mean, we're both girls!
ねぇ神様 どうしたらいいの？
Hey God, what should I do?
私 どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
ヘルプミー！
Help me!
なんか変だ 会いに来ても
Something is strange... Even if you come to see me...
今日も 年も 性別も 関係ない
Even today, age or gender doesn't matter!
けど けど けど
But, but, but...
三角形
Triangle,
三角形の恋はきまぐれ
A triangular love is whimsical,
一瞬で
In an instant,
一瞬でくずれるバランス
the balance crumbles.
普通の
A normal
普通の恋 夢見てたのに
I was dreaming of a normal love, but...
ノーマル設定の
With my normal settings,
わたしじゃ ちょっと無理ゲーすぎます
it's too much of an impossible game for me!
三角形
Triangle,
三角形の恋は不安定保存
A triangular love is unstable,
おしゃべりパピーぬいぐるみのフワモコだよ！
It's the Fuwamoko Talking Puppy Plushie!
ぎゅっとすると、いろいろ喋るよ！
If you squeeze us, we'll say all kinds of things!
どんなボイスが出るか、お楽しみに！
Look forward to hearing what voices we make!
We have Fuwawa to GO☆Finger Puppet!
Ooh! They both come with one extra Ruffian kigurumi costume you can dress us up in...
...and bring around with you everywhere!
フワワの指パペット！
Fuwawa's Finger Puppet!
どこでも一緒に連れていけるサイズで、着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もあるよ！
They're the perfect size to bring anywhere with you, and they come with a dress-up Ruffians costume!
Finally, we have two different ASMR Voice Packs! "Back from a Fluffy Date" with Fuwawa...
...and "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy" from Mococo!
ASMRボイスは、英語と日本語、両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in both English and Japanese!
My heart beats so fast! Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them! Ah!
The merch is separated into two sets: Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch!
If you purchase the Full Set, they come with bonuses, including a Cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはフワワセットとモココセットに分かれています！
The merch is split into a Fuwawa set and a Mococo set!
セットごとにチェキ風カードと特典ボイスが付きます！
Each set comes with a Cheki-style card and a bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セットは直筆サイン入りだよ！
The limited quantity set comes with a hand-written autograph!
We put lots of love into each and every signature, so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさんの愛情を込めてサイン書きますね！
We'll put lots of love into writing the signatures!
Please check out the Hololive Official Online Shop...
ぜひホロライブ公式ショップにチェックしてください！バウバウ！
Please check out the Hololive Official Shop! Bau Bau!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
What did you think of our birthday merch? Pretty cute, huh?
Yeah!
The reservations are going on sale right after the Birthday Live here ends...
So don't forget, okay?!
生誕のグッズの予約は...
The birthday merch reservations...
この後、開始しますので...
...will start right after this...
お忘れずにチェックしてくださいね！
...so please don't forget to check them out!
Yes! You can use the link below or on the side here!
Don't forget, okay??
We put a lot of love into it, and Icomochi-mama too!
Right after this ends, time to go, go, go!
Go buy it!
Wow, we performed modern special collab songs with our dear Senpais!
But there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right??
そう、まだ会ってない謎のゲストが一人いるんだよね！
That's right, there's still one mysterious guest we haven't met yet!
Well, should we give the Ruffians a hint first?
Ruffians, are you curious? Yeah!
Could it be...
Yagoo-san?
That's a good guess maybe, but...
We'll see, huh?
Maybe you should get ready...
...because you know, they aren't quite as bad as Pero...
...but they can get pretty nasty sometimes!
Mocochyan! You're not going to be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Especially before calling them out!
We'll see!
Well, let's get them out here then!
Could it be, could it be?!
Okay!
せーの、どうぞー！
On three, please come in!
わわわわ！来たしん！来たしんよ！来たしんよ！
Wa-wa-wa-wa! I'm here! I'm here! I'm here!
あーん、ちゅっ！
Mwah!
きゃあああ！ちゅっちゅ！
Kyaaaa! Mwah mwah!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃんです！わわわわー！
It's Kuro-chan! Wa-wa-wa-wa!
来たしんよ！
I'm here!
はじめまして！
Nice to meet you!
チワワじゃないよ、フワワだよ！
I'm not a Chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
フワワじゃないよ、モココだよ！
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo!
二人合わせて...
The two of us together...
フワモコです！バウバウ！
We are Fuwamoko! Bau Bau!
よろしくお願いします！
It's a pleasure to meet you!
フワモコのわちゃわちゃバースデーフェスティバルに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to Fuwamoko's chaotic Birthday Festival!
ハッピーバースデーだしんよ、フワモコ！
Happy birthday, Fuwamoko!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いいしんね！
Very nice!
ちょっとね、視聴者のラフィアンズもたくさんいると思いますけど...
I'm sure there are many Ruffians watching right now, but...
クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？
Could you explain what kind of person you are, Kuro-chan?
え？自分ですんの？これ！
Eh? I have to do it myself?
そうです！自己紹介！
Yes! Self-introduction!
わかったしんよ。だってこれ海外の人も見てますもんね？
Understood. Since overseas people are watching too, right?
海外の人もわかる自己紹介しますからね。
I'll do an intro that overseas people can understand.
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you, chu, chu, chu, chu, tulip!
え、困らないで？
Eh, don't look so troubled?
え、クロちゃんは...チューリップ？
Eh, Kuro-chan is... a tulip?
チューリップ？No, no, no, no!
A tulip? No, no, no, no!
ちょっとまだわからないかもしれないから...
Some people might still not understand, so...
えーとね、安田大サーカスっていうトリオを組んでる、えーと、芸人さんで...
Well, I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus...
あと豆柴の大群のプロデュースもやってますだし、作詞とかもしてます、クロちゃんです！
And I also produce Mameshiba no Taigun and write lyrics. I'm Kuro-chan!
お、おー！
Oh, wow!
じゃあ今度は英語でお願いします！
Then, this time, please do it in English!
English!
え？僕が？
Eh? Me?
Yes, 自分で！
Yes, yourself!
え、そんなこと急に言われたら、it's shy...
Eh, if you say that so suddenly, I'm shy...
Fuwawa...
言い訳は無し！
No excuses!
聞いてる？人の話
Are you listening to what people say?
頑張って、英語！
Do your best with English!
英語？ええと、なんなんだろうな。ええと...
English? Uh, let me see... what is it...
FuwaMoco comedian!
FuwaMoco comedians!
Idol producer. / いやいや、かっこいい！
Idol producer. / No way, that's cool!
やってるしんよ。 / おお、できる！
I'm doing it-shin! / Oh, you can do it!
クロちゃん、テレビでよく見てるけど...
We watch Kuro-chan on TV a lot, but...
ちょっとフワモコのペットのペロちゃんと、ええと、ちょっと似てるところがたくさんあるね。
You have a lot of similarities to our pet, Pero...
ちょっと、後ろの風船見てください！
Please look at the balloon behind us!
そっくりで、ペロです！
It looks exactly like Pero!
ちょっと待って、球体ってか丸いところが似てるだけじゃない？
Wait a second, isn't it just that we're both round?
そんなことない！ / 本当？
No way! / Really?
クロちゃんと似てるところは...
Where you're similar to Pero is...
嘘つきで、女の子好きで、いやらしい！うん！
You're a liar, you love girls, and you're nasty! Yeah!
だからね、見た目で騙されないで。
So, don't be fooled by your looks.
クロちゃんはそんなに言われて大丈夫なの？
Is it okay for them to say all that about you?
いや、酷い。悲しくなってきた。えーん、えーん、えーん！
Wow, that's harsh. I'm getting sad. *Wah, wah, wah!*
えんぽこえん、ふん。 / えー！
Enpokoen, hmph! / What!
全然、人のギャグを聞かないよね、君たちは。
You guys don't listen to other people's gags at all, do you?
できれば、クロちゃんは、ペロの友達になってくれませんか？
If possible, Kuro-chan, could you be Pero's friend?
フワモコの友達じゃなくて、ペロの友達になるの？
Not FuwaMoco's friend, but Pero's friend?
フワモコはクロちゃんと友達になりたくないから！
Because FuwaMoco doesn't want to be friends with Kuro-chan!
おかしくないそれ？いやいや、気持ち悪いから？
Isn't that weird? No, wait, because I'm gross?
気持ち悪くない、マニアには受ける！
I'm not gross, enthusiasts love me!
違う！気持ち悪い、やっぱり！
No! You are gross, after all!
モコちゃん、ちょっとやりすぎですよ、失礼です。
Moco-chan, that's a bit too much. It's rude.
いや、もし、もしもペロと仲良くなってほしいんだったら、フワモコちゃん、クロちゃんに可愛らしく頼んだ方がいいんじゃない？
Well, if you want me to get along with Pero, shouldn't you ask me nicely and cutely?
はぁ？
Huh?
NO!
NO!? しっかりとした否定！
NO!? That was a firm rejection!
え、ま、けどペロ可愛いから、仲良くなってもいいとは思ってるよ。
Well, but Pero is cute, so I think I wouldn't mind being friends.
あ、嬉しい嬉しい！可愛くないけど、仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいな！
Ah, I'm happy! You're not cute, but I'd be happy if you became friends!
感情が、感情が色々ありすぎるのよ、本当に。
Your feelings... there are just too many conflicting emotions here, seriously.
ま、ま、クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね？
Well, well, Kuro-chan is a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
そう、元々アイドルになろうと思ったのに、騙されて芸人にさせられたから、アイドルは本当に夢、ドリーム！
Yes, I originally wanted to be an idol, but I was tricked into becoming a comedian, so being an idol is really my dream!
なんか、悲しいな、かわいそう。でも、ドリームって大事ですから！
That's kind of sad, poor guy. But dreams are important!
そう！で、クロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから、もうせっかく、一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
Exactly! And since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol, why don't you sing with us?
あ、いいしん、いいしん！オッケーだしんよ！
Ah, sure, sure! It's okay-shin!
この曲を歌いましょう、この曲を！
Let's sing this song, this one!
あの、ハードル上げないで。 / 大張夫、大丈夫！
Um, don't raise the bar. / It's okay, it's okay!
アイドルのプロデューサーもやってるし、実力見せてよ！
You're an idol producer too, so show us your skills!
オッケーだしんよ、行くしん、行くしん！ / オッケー！
Okay-shin, here I go, here I go! / Okay!
じゃあ、すごく可愛い曲を、一緒に歌いましょう！
Then, let's sing a very cute song together!
え、何歌うの？楽しみ！ / オッケー！
Eh, what are we singing? I'm excited! / Okay!
さあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね。
Now, let's announce the title together.
せーの、ちゅ。多様性。
One, two... Chu. Tayousei.
多様性歌うの？！
We're singing Tayousei?!
我爱你 酔いが覚めない
Wo ai ni, I'm so intoxicated
Oh, I need you 恋が醒めない
Oh, I need you, I'm not clear-headed
お生憎様の慣れ果て 察して
Oh baby, I can't imagine what this mess will be
無問題 破滅してみて
Moumantai, go on, you're ruining it
hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma makes it
猛反対 お手 お座りで ハイ報酬
More like mine, so sit and let me make it worth your time
喉の奥がチクンチクン
I feel a tingle in the back of my throat
僕はドクンドクン
My heart's pounding, listen close
鼓動で孤独 消してみてよ
Drowning out how lonely I feel when you're not here with me
愛も恋も 独裁して
I want your love, so show me what I need
僕を独占して
Say that you'll monopolize me
このまま中毒になるまで チューしよ
Kiss me till we're greedy, addicted to this ecstasy
そして
So with it
get get get on! get get get on! get on chu!
get get get on! get get get get on chu!
熱くとろけるくらいに 溢れた気持ちが
Emotions overflowing, spilling out, escaping my mouth... It's melting hot
たまらないでしょ
Isn't it mesmerizing?
get get get on! get get get on! get on chu!
get get get on! get get get get on chu!
get on! get on!
我爱你 無問題
Wo ai ni, moumantai
get get get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン？勝負はいつも？トンチンカン
Pon, chii, kan? You should know it's a game I / Ton, chin, kan? Have always dominated
僕に言わせりゃ？ちんぷんかんぷんだ？最後はロンでしょ？
I've no clue of what the rules are, but I'll win with "rong"
もう何回？殺られればいい？
How much more? Will I have lost my mind?
oh, one night 忘れられない
Oh, one night of pleasure, can't forget it
終わんないでトキメキ恋愛♥予習
Don't let it end, this heartbeat love practice!
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat is tingling, tingling
僕はドクンドクン
And I'm thumping, thumping
心臓ごと 引きずり出して見せてよ
Drag out my heart and show me!
気持ちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, though it's a pain
やっぱ照れくさいけど
And it's embarrassing after all
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
Let's share a kiss we'll never forget until we die
いかれた街はゾンビで溢れる
This crazy town is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You are in love with me
ときめく胸につながるロープを引きなよ
Pull the rope connected to your throbbing heart
Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの愛しさが
A love so deep that it could make me go crazy...
美しいでしょ
...is beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
せーの
Ready, set...
ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Pon, chi, kan, it won't end!
Get Get Get on chu!
我愛你 無問題
Wo ai ni, mou mantai!
Get Get Get on chu!
わー！やったー！
Wow! We did it!
うまくいったしー！
It went so well!
よかったー！頑張ったね、クロちゃん！
I'm so glad! You did great, Kuro-chan!
楽しかった！ありがとう！
That was so fun! Thank you!
えー、ちょっとね、さよならする前に...
So, um, before we say goodbye...
えーっと、1個お願いしてもいいですか？
Um, can we ask you for one favor?
1個だけだしん？
Just one, shin?
はい、1個だけしん！
Yes, just one, shin!
えっと、フワモコは魔界の番犬で、バウバウをよく言っているんですけど...
Um, FUWAMOCO are demon guard dogs, and we often say "Bau Bau"...
クロちゃん、カメラに向かって、フワモコのように可愛いバウバウをしてもらえますか？
Kuro-chan, can you look at the camera and do a cute "Bau Bau" like FUWAMOCO?
えー！できるかしん？
What! Can I do it, shin?
行くしんよ！
Here we go, shin!
バウ！バウ！
Bau! Bau!
え、それがベスト？
Wait, is that your best?
もう一回！もっとやって！
One more time! Do it more!
バウ！バウ！
Bau! Bau!
実は、もう一個やりたいことがあるんですけど...
Actually, there's one more thing we want to do...
何？
What?
さきほどやりましたけど、フワモコはいつもやってる自己紹介があって...
We did it earlier, but FUWAMOCO has a self-introduction we always do...
できれば、3人で一緒にやりたいです！
If possible, we'd like to do it together with all three of us!
あ、あれ可愛かったから、やりたい！クロちゃんも！
Oh, that was cute, I want to do it too!
イェーイ！じゃあ行きますよ！
Yay! Here we go then!
オッケー！
Okay!
凍らすよ！フワワだよ！
I'll freeze you! I'm Fuwawa!
わー！フワワじゃないよ！クロちゃんだよ！
Wah! I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Kuro-chan!
あっ、クロちゃんじゃないよ！モココだよ！
Ah, it's not Kuro-chan! I'm Mococo!
3人合わせて...
And together we are...
いやいやいや！バウバウ！
No, no, no! Bau Bau!
ちょっとちょっと、クロちゃん！
Wait a minute, Kuro-chan!
もう、嘘とかつくなよね！
Don't lie to us anymore!
モココ、パンチしちゃう！
Mococo's gonna punch you!
えー！痛い痛い痛い！
Ah! It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
救急車、1台...
An ambulance, please...
いらないよ、もう嘘！
No need! No more lies!
プンプン！
Pout, pout!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて！
Calm down, calm down!
大丈夫、モコちゃん、大丈夫。
It's okay, Moco-chan, it's okay.
クロちゃんは、これからもみんなをいっぱい笑顔にして、素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
Kuro-chan, please keep making everyone smile and become a wonderful idol!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
じゃあ、モコちゃん、最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね。
Well, Moco-chan, let's end with a high-five for Kuro-chan and say goodbye.
仲直り、仲直り？
Reconciliation, reconciliation?
せーの、ハイタッチ！ハイタッチ！
Ready, high-five! High-five!
ほらほら！やってみて、やってみて！
Come on! Give it a try, give it a try!
デコピン！
Flick!
痛っ！なんで？ちょっと！ひどくない？
Ouch! Why?! Hey! Isn't that mean?
けど、フワモコちゃん、本当に、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
But FUWAMOCO, truly, happy birthday!
ありがとう！ありがとうしん！
Thank you! Thank you, shin!
きゅんからの、バッキュン！おめでとうハート！
Kyun and then... bam! Happy birthday heart!
バウバウ！レッツゴーン！
Bau Bau! Let's go-n!
わあ！すごーい！花火だー！たまやー！
Wow! Amazing! Fireworks! Tamaya!
Wow! That was so nice!
Things got really crazy, but I'm glad that you are happy!
なんか、クロちゃん凄すぎて、分かんなくなってきたかも！
Like, Kuro-chan was so incredible, I think I'm starting to lose track of what's happening!
But we still have one more, one more very exciting thing to share with you!
Yes! まだまだ楽しみがあるよ！
Yes! We still have more fun in store!
Maybe... what is it? Can you guess what it is?
何かな？何かな？
What could it be? What could it be?
Well, FUWAMOCO are at our first anniversary!
We were able to release our very first original song!
Going to be a ballad!
And then for our second anniversary, we were able to release Lifetime Showtime!
Our original song that's been on with us along this journey!
Yeah, very special song.
And you know, for FuwaMoco, singing and dancing is something that means so much to us!
Yeah, music! And Ruffians...
...might have heard that you'd like to hear more from us, too, right?
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! What do you think?
Well...
Our announcement is...
Drumroll! Okay, drumroll, Ruffians!
Prrrrrrrrrr...
A new original song!
Yes! Original song!
And this song, it's extra special!
It's written by none other than the legendary rock idol song composer, Matsukuma Kenta-san!
Who works with many famous idol groups, wow!
Also written music for the idol group that Kuro-chan produces, MAMESHiBA NO TAiG0!
But Ruffians, you might be a little bit surprised, okay?
So get ready!
Ruffians... with this song...
...we'd like to express our roughest feelings as demon dogs.
DEMON'S RESiDENCE.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE / 作詞：海野水玉 作曲：松隈ケンタ 編編：SCRAMBLES
[Title: DEMON'S RESIDENCE / Lyrics: Mizutama Umino, Music: Kenta Matsukuma, Arrangement: SCRAMBLES]
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」 ネオンの脇を抜け
"Buddy, where shall we go?" Slipping past the neon lights
バブルガムがはじけたら let's go
When the bubblegum pops, let's go
最低な夜を潜って 僕らは群れをなす
Slinking through this wretched night, we run in a pack
「あの頃よりもマシだね」 my way
"Better than back then, huh?" my way
「不完全なんです」 首輪をつけた
"It's incomplete," wearing a collar
良い子なんかじゃもうイヤ Ah!!
I'm already fed up with being a good girl, ah!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 噛みついていけ
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, bite down!
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
気分はどうだい 泣いているのかい
How do you feel? Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって 叫んでいたいんだ stray dogs
Rip the chains apart, I want to keep screaming, stray dogs
彼方へと 飛ぶ鳥を
Flying towards the distant horizon...
見上げるだけかい それでいいのかい
Is that all you do? Is that enough?
燃えるなら ほら青く
If you're going to burn, then look, burn blue
「説教なんかいらない」 スプレー缶振って
"I don't need any lectures," shaking a spray paint can
イタズラ書きで彩る runway
Coloring the runway with graffiti
愛情なんか coin toss 誰に bet するのか
Love is just a coin toss, who are you going to bet on?
不確定要素ばかりね lonely
It's just full of uncertain factors, lonely
二人でひとつと決めた
We decided on one for the two of us
あの目を忘れない Ah!!
I won't forget those eyes, ah!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 満天の空
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, a sky full of stars
あの星がひどく不快で
That star is terribly unpleasant
勝利は上々だ 味はするのかい
Victory is splendid, can you taste it?
鎖を噛んで 唸っていたいんだ stray dogs 僕ら
Biting the chains, I want to keep growling, stray dogs, us
宇宙さえも撃ち落として
Shooting down even the universe
見下ろす奈落 ビルは輝く
Looking down at the abyss, the buildings shine
LOL Now I am free!!
Woah-oh-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh...
孤独を分け合い食べた
Sharing and eating our loneliness
あの日を忘れない Ah!!
I won't forget that day, ah!
夜を睨んだ stray dogs そうだ
Staring at the night, stray dogs, that's right
怪物は世界のほうさ
The monster is the world itself
抜け出せるのかい 足は動くかい
Can you escape? Can your legs move?
走るなら今
If you're going to run, do it now
DEMON'S RESIDENCE stray dogs 僕ら
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, stray dogs, us
この街を駆け抜けて行け
Run through this city
地獄の果てに何が見えるかい
What can you see at the end of hell?
鎖をちぎって 叫んでいたいんだ stray dogs 僕ら
Rip the chains apart, I want to keep screaming, stray dogs, us
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
君ならどうだい 共に駆けるかい
How about you? Will you run with me?
夜明けが合図だ
Dawn is the signal...
行こう
Let's go!
Bau bau!
Thank you for always being here for us!
Please listen to...
side by side!
Finally we made it through but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on it's the heart that we will follow
We'll move on passed the heartbreak and the sorrow if you
Stay by my side
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though there's been rough times where nobody wanted us,
we kept going, and we kept dreaming,
now we are here,
we're not alone anymore!
We'll be here together. We have smiles to protect!
C'mon, let's go!
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nya nya
Bau bau!
Thank you for the encore, Ruffians!
That was side by side!
Bau bau!
We're really happy to sing side by side for you for the first time live today!
Yeah! 初披露できてとっても嬉しかったです！
Yeah! We are so happy we got to perform it live for the first time!
Yeah, side by side is a song made by Aiobahn-san,
but also between FuwaMoco!
Yeah, it is!
We know it's a song that you love a lot,
but we also do because it's very special to us
since it's the ending theme for a visual novel that we care about...
Nekopara!
Nekopara! Bau bau!
And with this song, our dream of singing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
Yeah!
そう、この曲で、Fuwamocoの夢、美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
That's right, with this song, FuwaMoco's dream of singing the theme song for a bishojo game has come true!
It came true! Thank you! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
And thank you so much for joining us for a special day again this year.
It's been a dream, Ruffians!
And we know it's all because of you that we're able to be here
and do all the amazing things that we do, so thank you.
Thank you!
It's sad to say, but...
あ！次の歌は…最後の歌です。
Ah! This next song... is our last song.
えー！
Aw...
でも、特別だよ！
But, you know... it's a very special one.
フワモコは魔界の番犬として、みんなの笑顔を守るためにここにいるんだよね！
You know, FUWAMOCO, as demon guard dogs, we're here to protect your smile, right?
これからもそうしていくよ。笑顔を守るために！
We will continue to do that. To protect your smile!
アイドルとして、全力でね！
Yeah, doing our all as idols!
それに、ふわふわでもこもこな魂もね！
And just as our fluffy and fuzzy souls, too!
何千年も、何万年も、魔界の犬の歳としてここに居続けるよ！
We'll continue to be here for thousands and thousands of demon dog years.
毎日が当たり前じゃないってことを思い出しながらね。
All while remembering that everyday isn't given.
当たり前なことなんて何一つないからね。
We don't take anything for granted.
だから落ち込んだ時は、私たちがいつでもここで応援してるって思い出してね！
And you know, when you're down, we hope you'll remember that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
うん！ラフィアンズを全力で応援するよ！
Yes! We'll cheer you on, Ruffians!
だから、今日の最後の曲の歌詞を、よーく聴いててね！
So, please listen closely to the lyrics of our last song for today!
明日も
May tomorrow...
明後日も
...and the day after too...
あなたが笑ってますように
...I hope you will be laughing...
ずっと
...forever.
Lala...
ラフィアンズ、今日は私たちの誕生日を一緒に過ごしてくれて本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much Ruffians for spending our birthday with us today!
辛い時はいつでもこの歌を思い出して、私たちがそばにいることを忘れないでね。
Please think of this song whenever things are rough, and know that we'll be here.
この最後の歌をみんなに贈ります。
This last song is for you.
「Wishful Garnet」！
Wishful Garnet!
過去を振り返ると 思い出す
When I look back at the past, I remember
ガーネットの空 溢れてく 光
The light overflowing from the garnet sky
この瞳に映し出された あの日は
The day reflected in these eyes of mine
美しく 揺れる
Sways beautifully
What do you think?
紅く 滲んだ空に
To the sky tinged with red...
願いました どうかこの願い
...I made a wish, please let this wish...
届けてください
...reach you.
明日も
May tomorrow...
明後日も
...and the day after too...
あなたが笑ってますように
...I hope you will be laughing.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are apart...
前を向けますように
...I hope you can keep looking forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you...
わたしが壊してあげる
...I will break them for you.
もう負けないで
Do not give up...
進むこと
...keep moving forward.
いつでもそばにいるから
Because I will always be by your side.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are separated,
前を向けますように
I hope you can keep facing forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
I will break the chains
わたしが壊してあげる
that bind you.
もう負けないで進むこと
Don't give up, keep moving forward,
いつでもそばに
because I will always
あなたのそばに
be by your side,
わたしはいつもいるから
here for you.
Lalala...
Yeah... yeah...
Bau bau!
Thank you so much, Ruffians!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership, okay?
Bau bau!